(Penny:)I know, right?
(Leonard:)Hey, what took
you guys so long?
(Priya:)Oh, we were
just chatting.
(Leonard:)That's nice.
What about?
(Priya:)We were just
comparing notes
(Penny:)about how you are
in the sack.
(Leonard:)That's funny.
Yeah.
(Raj:)What if she
wasn't kidding?
(Leonard:)It doesn't matter.
(Leonard:)I'm the king of foreplay.
(Howard:)Hey, how'd it go?
(Bernadette:)You're a putz.
(Bernadette:)You know what that means?
(Howard:)Yeah. Do you?
(Bernadette:)Your mother just
taught it to me.
(Bernadette:)She thinks she got food
poisoning from that deli
(Bernadette:)and she just wanted
to make sure I was okay.
(Howard:)And are you?
(Bernadette:)No, because I'm
engaged to a putz.
(Bernadette:)You let me believe I was the
reason she had a heart attack.
(Howard:)Well, based on the
available evid--
(Bernadette:)Shut up!
(Bernadette:)She said I'm
a wonderful girl
(Bernadette:)and that you're
lucky to have me.
(Howard:)Where are you going?
(Bermadette(in a voice like Mrs Wolowitz):)To the toilet!